imagespacemedia.com 2014-07-02

# Vibrant Media — The Global Leader of In–Content Contextual Technology

Vibrant Media, Inc. (“ **Vibrant Media** ” “ **we** " or “ **us** ”) helps clients serve more relevant content and advertisements. We provide this privacy policy so we may inform you about how our technology (" **Technology** ") processes information for online advertisers, website owners, and other businesses that use our services (our "Clients"). This policy also outlines our privacy practices on our corporate Website (" **Website** "), [www.vibrantmedia.com](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/ "Vibrant Media"). If you have questions regarding our privacy and data practices, please contact us by [clicking here](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/about/contact.asp?ref=privacy "Contact Vibrant"). By using the Website, you accept the policies and restrictions set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Topics:**

  1. Collection and Use of Information on this Website
  2. Collection and Use of Information through Our Technology
  3. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
  4. Controlling the Collection and Use of Information
  5. Participation in Self-Regulatory Programs
  6. Information Security
  7. Changes to this Privacy Policy
  8. Who can I ask if I have additional questions?

### 1\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE

_Personally Identifiable Information._ This Website is directed to our Clients and prospective Clients, who are businesses. The Website is not directed to consumers. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") via this Website when a visitor voluntarily provides it to us. PII means name, postal address, email address and telephone number. We may use that information to respond to your requests and inquiries and for other purposes. The following are some examples of specific use cases:

  * _Vibrant Media's Inquiry Form_ – The Vibrant Media Website contains an "inquiry form" for Clients and prospective Clients to request additional information about Vibrant Media’s products and services. Vibrant Media uses contact information (e.g., name and email address) provided via the inquiry form to respond to requests from Clients and prospective Clients, and to help us provide excellent customer service to our Clients.
  * _Business Client Registration_ – As part of the business Client registration process, Clients may be required to provide some PII. We may use this information to contact the Client if there is a billing or order processing issue, to help us process invoices, and to otherwise provide our services to our Clients.
  * _Testimonials_ – Some of our Clients agree to allow us to use their name and comments on the Website as part of testimonials. If you’ve agreed to have your name appear in a testimonial on this Website, you should be aware that your name and comment as well as other information displayed can be read, collected, or used by other users of this Website.

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information._ We may collect Non-PII from visitors to this Website. Non-PII includes information such as your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to this Website, the referring URL and your computer's operating system. We may use this information for purposes including managing, operating, and enhancing the Website.

_Cookies_ We use cookies on this Website. Cookies are small text files placed in a visitor’s browser. Cookies make using our Website easier for visitors by, among other things, saving their login preferences and improving the usability of our Website. Through your browser settings, you may disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Website may not function properly or may be considerably slower. For more information about cookies please visit the Vibrant Media Cookie Statement by clicking here.

_Third Party Websites_ The Website may contain links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Vibrant Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of all websites that you visit.

_Updating / Deleting your PII_ If you'd like us to update, correct, or delete any PII that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us by clicking here and we will process your request.

Back to Top

### 2\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION THROUGH OUR TECHNOLOGY

_Overview of the Technology._ Our Clients may use our Technology to deliver digital advertisements and other content that are intended to align with consumers' current interests. This form of advertising, called "Interest Matching", delivers advertisements that are more relevant, interesting, and useful for consumers. Our Clients may also use our Technology for other purposes including to help measure the effectiveness of a campaign or to optimize other campaigns.

_Collection and Use of Information._ Our Technology is designed to facilitate the delivery of contextual and interest-based advertising. We may use our Technology to identify a visitor's interests by gathering web viewing data (e.g., web pages visited, interactions with ads, words or other content displayed in a browser or device) and other non-PII (e.g., browser type, referring URL, Internet service provider, computer's or device’s operating system, and date and time of visits) via cookies and other technologies. We may also collect and use other Non-PII including a data set of keyword interactions, which we may use to provide more relevant advertisements and help manage our advertising campaigns. This data set may include keywords recently displayed on a computer or device, the time and date one of our Client's advertisements was clicked on or displayed, and the web pages viewed after interaction with our Client's advertisements. We may use this information to make inferences about the interests or preferences associated with a particular browser or device. These inferences are used to help make the online advertisements that visitors see more relevant to them. Web viewing data and non-PII is also used for other purposes including ad delivery and reporting, measuring the effectiveness of a campaign, optimizing a campaign, and for operational purposes.

We may combine non-PII with information (e.g., demographic data) provided by other entities to help make our clients' advertising more relevant. Some of these entities that provide data to us participate in self-regulatory programs including the Digital Advertising Alliance's ("DAA") program. To learn about the DAA program as well as exercise choice with respect to those entities participating in the DAA program, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/ "About Ads").

Visitors may encounter our Technology when they visit a web site: (1) where one of our Clients has enabled our advertising solution; (2) where Vibrant Media, or one of our Clients, purchases online advertisements; and/or (3) where one of our Clients places a web beacon or similar functioning technology. A consumer may "opt out" of certain practices as explained below. 

_Storage of Non-Personally Identifiable Information._ We retain the Non-PII collected via our Technology for up to 13 months. After 13 months, we remove the cookie identification number and IP addresses and store it for up to 5 years to maintain financial records as well as for data analytics purposes. For more information about how we use cookies, please visit our Cookie Statement [www.vibrantmedia.com/cookies.asp](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/cookies.asp "Vibrant Cookies page").

Back to Top

### 3\. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties 

_General._ We may at our discretion disclose PII and Non-PII (" **Information** ") to third parties if we believe disclosure is necessary by law, or to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. We also may disclose Information when necessary to comply with a court order, legal process or other legal proceeding. Finally, we may transfer Information to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, partial or total sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

_PII._ We may share PII with service providers who provide services for us. These service providers are restricted from using the information we provide for purposes other than performing services at our direction.

_Non-PII._ We may share aggregate Non-PII collected by us with third parties for a variety of purposes such as analytics. For example, we may disclose to our Clients that 'blue banner ads' receive more clicks than 'orange banner ads.'

Back to Top

### 4\. CONTROLLING THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

If you'd like to learn how to opt-out from having Vibrant Media collect and use Non-PII from your computer or device in connection with our Technology for Interest Matching advertising, please [click here](http://intellitxt.com/opt_out/ch_optout.asp "Opting Out from Interest Matching"). When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your browser. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect Non-PII from a particular browser or device to tailor our online advertisement campaigns. You will still receive ads if you opt out from Vibrant, but these ads may be less relevant to you. In addition, we may continue to collect certain data for basic ad serving and other purposes such as counting the number of times a keyword has been clicked or other analytic purposes. Please note that if you delete or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. If you block cookies, your opt-out choice also may not be effectuated.

Back to Top

### 5\. PARTICIPATION IN SELF-REGULATORY PROGRAMS

We support the cross industry, Self-Regulatory Principles as managed by the DAA (" **DAA** ") (for more information [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/ "About Ads")). To provide consumers with enhanced transparency, we display the DAA’s Ad Choices Icon in advertisements delivered across our network to help make consumers aware of how data is being collected and used and to provide choices for consumers who want more control. Vibrant Media also is a member of (1) the Internet Advertising Bureau (“IAB”) and abides by IAB’s Member Code of Conduct, which you can review by [clicking here](http://www.iab.net/public_policy/codeofconduct "IAB")and (2) is an NAI member and adheres to the NAI Code of Conduct (“ **NAI** ”) opt-out tool for behavioral advertising, which you can review at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "NAI Opt-out tool").

Our Clients may separately collect Non-PII or other information from consumers. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of our Clients, and we are not responsible for their collection of Non-PII or other information from you. 

Back to Top

### 6\. Information Security

The security of your information is important to us, including but not limited to the PII collected via the Website. We have implemented security measures to help protect the information we maintain. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Back to Top

### 7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may modify this privacy policy from time to time. Please return here frequently to review this privacy policy.

Back to Top

###  8\. Who can I ask if I have additional questions?

If you have any questions or comments about [www.vibrantmedia.com](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/ "Vibrant Media") or about this privacy policy, please contact:

**Via mail:** Vibrant Media, Inc. 565 Fifth Avenue, 16th Floor, New York, NY 10017   
**Via email:** [info@vibrantmedia.com](mailto:info@vibrantmedia.com "Contact Vibrant")   
**Via telephone:** (646) 312-6100

Or you can submit an inquiry here. 

Back to Top

Last updated April 24, 2014
